翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
Instantiating arrays is a lot like instantiating any other object.
实例化数组与实例化任何其他对象非常相似
So I'll first note that arrays are also objects.
首先要注意的是，数组也是对象
So what's an object?
那么什么是对象呢？
Well, that's like a planet, or a walrus, or a dog, or whatever else.
比如说一颗行星、一只海象、一只狗或者其他任何东西
But it also includes arrays.
也包括数组
And as we've seen, objects are usually instantiated using the new keyword.
正如我们所看到的，对象通常使用 new 关键字实例化
So I might say, planet p equals new planet, yada, yada, yada.
我可以说 Planet p = new Planet()
Or I could say, integrate x equals new int,
或者 int[] x = new int[]
and then use this syntax that we saw in homework zero.
然后使用作业0中看到的语法
Now, in the previous lecture, we broke down declaration, instantiation, and assignment into separate steps.
在上一节课中，我们将声明、实例化和赋值分解为单独的步骤
So let's just do that again in the context of arrays to make sure that everything all makes sense.
我们在这里再过一次，确保理解所有内容
So when I say int array a, this is a declaration.
int[] a 是一个声明
What that does is it creates a box, which is 64 bits in size, which can store the address of int array, and nothing else.
它创建一个64位的盒子，只存储 int 数组的地址
Even though, technically, int arrays, and planets, and walruses, and so forth,
从技术上讲，int 数组、行星、海象这些对象
all those variables store 64 bit addresses,
它们的变量都存储64位地址
the compiler will only let us store an address of an int array in this box.
编译器只允许我们在这个盒子中存储 int 数组的地址
Now, at this point, there is no actual object,
没有实际的对象
so we've only declared a variable.
所以仅仅声明了一个变量
Next up, there's instantiation.
接下来是实例化
So when I say new int braces 0, 1, 2, 95, 4,
当执行 new int[] ｛0, 1, 2, 95, 4｝时
that will instantiate a new object--
它将实例化一个新的对象
that is, it will create 5 boxes, each of size 32.
也就是说它将创建5个盒子，每个32位
It'll put 0, 1, 2, 95, and 4 in those boxes, respectively.
分别将0、1、2、95和4放入这些盒子中
And then the new command will return the address of this object.
然后 new 命令返回该对象的地址
Now, at this point, I'll say that object is anonymous,
此时这个对象是匿名的
in the sense that there is no name for it, right?
也就是说它没有名字
We haven't assigned it to a variable.
我们还没有将它赋给变量
The address is shouted by new, but it falls on deaf ears.
new 高呼它的地址，但无人理睬
And so while this object is created,
因此这个对象被创建
it is immediately gone--
马上就消失了
or just not usable.
或者只是无法使用
So I should mention very briefly that an array is not actually literally only 5 times 32 bits.
我应该简单提一下，一个数组实际上并不是字面上的5乘以32位
There's a little bit of additional overhead not shown here, but not really a big deal in our class.
还有一些额外的开销没有显示，但在我们的课中无关紧要
And then often, we will do declaration, instantiation, and assignment all in one step.
通常我们会一次性完成声明、实例化和赋值
So here it is.
就像这样
The declaration part of this line,
这一行的声明部分
it creates a 64 bit box for storing an address.
创建用于存储地址的64位盒子
New int creates this int array.
new int[] 创建 int 数组
And then finally, the equals sign takes the address shouted by new.
最后等号获取了 new 报告的地址
And this time, rather than falling on deaf ears and not ever being known, it is stored in the a variable.
这次它存储在 a 中，而不是置之不理
So just to finish out this little section,
为了讲完这一小部分
I figured I'd mention the fact that instantiated objects--
我想我应该说明，实例化的对象
that is, planets, arrays, or whatever else-- can be lost.
也就是行星、数组或其他任何东西，它们都可能丢失
So in other words, let's say a points at this object right here, and it's the only copy.
换句话说，a 指向的这个对象是它的唯一副本
It's the only copy of the address, this 64 bit box here.
这是地址的唯一副本，这个64位的盒子
In that case, if we were to say a equals new whatever else,
在这种情况下，如果让 a 等于新的东西
right-- so a points at a new object--
比如指向一个新的对象
then we no longer have this address stored anywhere.
那么这个地址就不再存储在任何地方了
And therefore, there's no way we can ever get that object back.
我们没办法再拿到那个对象了
Now, that's not a bad thing.
这不是一件坏事
I mean, there are cases, as we'll see pretty soon when we start building lists,
有些情况，我们很快就会看到，当我们开始建立 List 时
where we do actually want to lose references to things.
我们确实想丢失对象的引用
But just a note, we lose an address,
我们丢失一个地址
that object is lost, and will be consumed by the garbage collector.
这个对象就会丢失，并由垃圾收集器处理
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）